https://nnpdf.org/about-us/nnpdf-privacy-policy/

FDA Approved Clinical Trials
Cyclo Therapeutics, Inc.
Surveys/Market Research
Home »
NNPDF Privacy Policy
NNPDF Privacy Policy
NNPDF Privacy Policy
The National Niemann-Pick Disease Foundation is committed to safeguarding each user’s privacy while viewing the NNPDF website.  The NNPDF does collect demographic information on the number of hits, number of unique visitors, etc. to help us improve the site.
The NNPDF website does provide links to other sites that might be of interest to those who use the site.  The NNPDF is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites.
The NNPDF Board of Directors, Staff, Consultants and Volunteers are committed to maintaining the privacy for all persons that contact the NNPDF.  Information voluntarily provided by visitors to the site through email or forms is not sold to other organizations. Information may be shared with the Board of Directors, Staff, Consultants and Volunteers to provide a proper response to questions or concerns.
Any personal information revealed by users visiting the NNPDF social media platforms that are open to the public can be collected and used by others.  The NNPDF is not responsible for the content or any viewpoints, ideas, proposals, information and other intellectual property posted on these social media platforms.
The NNPDF reserves the right to amend or alter its site privacy policy at any time without notice by posting such change to the NNPDF website.
09/28/2017 jjb
Share this!FacebookTwitterInstagram
NNPDF Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2020 National Niemann-Pick Disease FoundationPO Box 49, Fort Atkinson, WI 53538-0049 | 877-287-3672 | nnpdf@nnpdf.org
The National Niemann-Pick Disease Foundation (NNPDF) does not engage in the practice of medicine. It is not a medical authority nor does it claim to have medical knowledge. This site is an educational service of the National Niemann-Pick Disease Foundation and is not meant to provide diagnostic or treatment advice. Information contained or suggested on this Web site does not constitute medical advice. For all information related to care, medication or treatment, the NNPDF recommends consulting a physician to determine if information presented is applicable. Please review these additional cautions about medical information provided on the Internet.
This Web site is a service of the National Niemann-Pick Disease Foundation's Family Services Program, made possible by the financial support of our member families and other generous donors and grantors. This site receives no government funding, nor does it host or receive funding from advertising or from the display of commercial content.
The National Niemann-Pick Disease Foundation is a 501(c)(3) organization.
Your donations are fully tax-deductible.
